Finding Aid for Michigan United Conservation Clubs records, 1937-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- People File
  - 9x6 Envelopes
    - Titus, Harold (Opie) (Box 23)
    - Tody, Wayne (Box 23)
    - Toepp, John (Box 23)
    - Tomboulian, Rep. Alice (Box 23)
    - Torres, Richard S. (Box 23)
    - Tower, Charles (Box 23)
    - Train, Russell (Box 23)
    - Traxler, Robert (Box 23)
    - Treadway, Tim (Box 23)
    - Trim, Claude A. (Box 23)
    - Trippensee, Reuben (Box 23)
    - Trimberger, E. John (Box 23)
    - Trombley, Ray (Box 23)
    - Trost, Fred (Box 23)
    - Troutman, Martin A. (Box 23)
    - Truchan, James (Box 23)
    - Tucker, Theodore R. (Box 23)
    - Turner, John F. (Box 23)
    - Turney, William G. (Box 23)
    - Ulman, Dwight (Box 23)
    - Udall, Stewart (Box 23)
    - Vaarberg, John (Box 23)
    - Van Buren, Mike (Box 23)
    - Vander Laan, Robert (Box 23)
    - Vanderwal, Rudolph (Box 23)
    - Van Frankenhuyzen, Gjtsbert (Box 23)
    - Van Keulen, Joyce (Box 23)
    - Vanloon, James (Box 23)
    - Van Putten, Mark (Box 23)
    - Van Regenmorter, William (Box 23)
    - Van Singel, Donald (Box 23)
    - Van Slooten, Marion (Box 23)
    - Varga, Ilona (Box 23)
    - Varnum, Charles H. (Box 23)
    - Vaughn, Ed (Box 23)
    - Vaughn, Jackie III (Box 23)
    - VerBerkmoes, Robert E. (Box 23)
    - Verme, Louis J. (Box 23)
    - Vitek, Joseph (Box 23)
    - Voelker, John (Box 23)
    - Vogt, John E. (Box 23)
    - Vogt, Joseph E. (Box 23)
    - Vohwinkle, Leroy (Box 23)
    - Voss, Ray (Box 23)
    - Voorhees, Harold J. (Box 23)
    - Vorva, Jerry (Box 23)
    - Walberg, Timothy L. (Box 23)
    - Walker, Barbara (Box 23)
    - Walker, Charles (Box 23)
    - Walker, Christopher (Box 23)
    - Walker, Gaylord (Box 23)
    - Walkinshaw, Lawrence H. (Box 23)
    - Wallace, Alice (Box 23)
    - Wallace, George J. (Box 23)
    - Wallace, Ted (Box 23)
    - Warbach, Oscar (Ozz) (Box 23)
    - Ward, Lynn (Box 23)
    - Warren, Tom (Box 23)
    - Wartner, Paul (Box 23)
    - Washington, Sam (Box 23)
    - Watkins, Juanita (Box 23)
    - Watson, Richard (Box 23)
    - Weatherspoon, Donald B. (Box 23)
    - Webb, Wilfred (Box 23)
    - Webster, Dr. Henry (Box 23)
    - Weeks, Donald (Box 23)
    - Weeks, Lloyd F. (Box 23)
    - Weeks, Mark (Box 23)
    - Wege, Peter (Box 23)
    - Weiss, Jeanette Short (Box 23)
    - Welborn, John (Box 23)
    - Welborn, Robert A. (Box 23)
    - Welling, Gerald (Box 23)
    - Welsh, Thomas S. (Box 23)
    - Wenk, Roger (Box 23)
    - Westfall, Marshall A. (Box 23)
    - Wetters, Howard (Box 23)
    - Whippen, William (Box 23)
    - White, Stewart Edward (Box 23)
    - Whiteley, Harry H. (Box 23)
    - Whiting, Robert (Box 23)
    - Whitmore, John (Box 23)
    - Whyman, Deborah (Box 23)
    - Wichert, David A. (Box 23)
    - Wicks, James (Box 23)
    - Wiegand, Michelle S. (Box 23)
    - Wierzbicki, Rep. Frank V. (Box 23)
    - Wietecha, Christopher (Box 23)
    - Wilcox, David (Box 23)
    - Willard, Karen S. (Box 23)
    - Williams, Hank (Box 23)
    - Williams, Harvey A. (DAD) (Box 23)
    - Willison, Brent (Box 23)
    - Willitts, Lucille (Box 23)
    - Willoughby, L. Jean (Box 23)
    - Wilson, Dana F. (Box 23)
    - Wilson, Keith Edward (Box 23)
    - Winkelman, Babe (Box 23)
    - Wise, Carrie (Box 23)
    - Wojcik, Bruce (Box 23)
    - Wolf, Earl (Box 23)
    - Wolfe, Joan L. (Box 23)
    - Wolpe, Howard (Box 23)
    - Wood, Jim (Box 23)
    - Wood, Robert D. (Box 23)
    - Wood, Robert G. (Box 23)
    - Woodford, John (Box 23)
    - Worth, Jean (Box 23)
    - Wozniak, Chester (Box 23)
    - Wright, Asa (Box 23)
    - Yankee, David (Box 23)
    - Yeager, Fran (Box 23)
    - Yerkey, Judith (Box 23)
    - Yoder, Troy (Box 23)
    - Yokich, Tracey A. (Box 23)
    - Youatt, William G. (Box 23)
    - Young, C. Clifton (Box 23)
    - Young, Joseph F., Jr. (Box 23)
    - Young, Joseph F. Sr. (Box 23)
    - Young, Richard A. (Box 23)
    - Young, Robert (Box 23)
    - Younglove, Charles G. (Box 23)
    - Zavislak, James (Box 23)
    - Zelenko, Sue (Box 23)
    - Zern, Ed (Box 23)
    - Zettle, Donald G. (Box 23)
    - Ziegler, Hal (Box 23)
    - Zuidema, Michael R. (Box 23)
    - Zurawski, Paul (Box 23)
    - Zuverink, Gordon (Box 23)
- People File
  - 8.5x11 Envelopes
    - Anderson, Gary (Box 24)
    - Bagley, John H. (Box 24)
    - Bateman, Robert (Box 24)
    - Bear, Fred (Box 24)
      (world famous hunter)
    - Bedford, James (Box 24)
    - Bengel, Russell (Box 24)
    - Bennane, Michael J. (Box 24)
    - Boushelle, Gary (Box 24)
    - Carr, Robert (Box 24)
    - Cederberg, Elford A. (Box 24)
    - Chiapetta, Jerry (Box 24)
    - Ciaramitaro, Nick (Box 24)
    - Clark, George (Box 24)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box 24)
    - Coheleach, Guy (Box 24)
    - Crutcher, John (Box 24)
    - Curwood, James Oliver (Box 24)
    - Darling, Jay N. (Ding) (Box 24)
    - Davenport, Earl (Box 24)
    - Davis, Robert W. (Box 24)
    - Dingell, John, Jr. (Box 24)
    - Dingell, John, Sr. (Box 24)
    - East, Ben (Box 24)
    - Easterbrook, Bob (Box 24)
    - Esch, Marvin (Box 24)
    - Faxon, Jack (Box 24)
    - Fitzgerald, Sen. William (Box 24)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box 24)
    - Gaines, Harry R. (Box 24)
    - Gillette, Genevieve (Box 24)
    - Glassen, Harold (Box 24)
    - Gore, Al (Box 24)
    - Griffin, Robert P. (Box 24)
    - Griffiths, Martha W. (Box 24)
    - Guidry, Ron (Box 24)
    - Havens, David (Box 24)
    - Herbert, Paul A. (Box 24)
    - Hertel, Curtis (Box 24)
    - Hertel, John (Box 24)
    - Hillstead, David (Box 24)
    - Huggler, Tom (Box 24)
    - Ingle, Don (Box 24)
    - Inman, Donald (Box 24)
    - Jerome, George H. (Box 24)
    - Kadar, George (Box 24)
    - Keeler, Roy (PA) (Box 24)
    - Keller, Myrl (Box 24)
    - Kelley, Frank (Box 24)
    - Kelly, Larry (Box 24)
    - Kildee, Dale E. (Box 24)
    - Knight, Mickey M.L. (Box 24)
    - Levin, Carl (Box 24)
    - Levin, Sander (Box 24)
    - Lievense, Stan (Box 24)
    - Lindner, Al (Box 24)
    - LoCicero, Thomas V. (Box 24)
    - Lowe, Kenneth S. (Box 24)
    - Lujan, Manuel (Box 24)
    - Mathieu, Thomas C. (Box 24)
    - Matthews, Frank Sr. (Box 24)
    - Mayk, Rich (Box 24)
    - McDivitt, James A. (Box 24)
    - McGregor, Louis D. (Box 24)
    - McManus, Patrick (Box 24)
    - Mershon, William B. (Box 24)
    - Michalski, Louis B. (Box 24)
    - Miller, Jeffrey (Box 24)
    - Miller, Johnny (Box 24)
    - Milliken, William G. (Box 24)
    - Mottl, Harry (Box 24)
    - MUCC Presidents (Box 24)
    - Myers, O. Stewart (Box 24)
    - Nedzi, Lucien N. (Box 24)
    - Neff, Mort (Box 24)
    - O'Hara, James G. (Box 24)
    - Oppenheim, Keith (Box 24)
    - Oprea, Terrence (Box 24)
    - Ozoga, John J. (Box 24)
    - Page, Warren (Box 24)
    - Peterson, Roger Tory (Box 24)
    - Pfeiffer, George (Box 24)
    - Postupalsky, Sergej 1981 (Box 24)
    - Pursell, Carl D. (Box 24)
    - Rice, George (Box 24)
    - Riegle, Donald (Box 24)
    - Roach, Gary (Box 24)
    - Romney, George (Box 24)
    - Rue, Leonard Lee III (Box 24)
    - Runco, William J. (Box 24)
    - Ruppe, Philip E. (Box 24)
    - Sawyer, Harold (Box 24)
    - Scholle, August (Gus) (Box 24)
    - Shiras, George 3d (Box 24)
    - Smith, Richard P. (Box 24)
    - Squibb, Harry (Pete) (Box 24)
    - Stabile, James (Box 24)
    - Sterling, Tom (Box 24)
    - Upton, Fred (Box 24)
    - Vander Jagt, Guy (Box 24)
    - Van Frankenhuyzen, Gijsbert (Box 24)
    - Washington, Tom (Box 24)
    - Welborn, John A. (Box 24)
    - Wendler, Paul H. (Box 24)
    - Wonser, Cash H. (Box 24)
    - Young, C. Clifton (Box 24)
    - Younglove, Charles G. (Box 24)
    - Zollar, Charles (Box 24)
- Scrapbooks
  There are two Scrapbooks in this record group. The larger scrapbook contains MUCC awards, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, etc. from around the 1950s and 1960s. The smaller scrapbook (boxed) contains articles, clippings, and some correspondence from 1945-1963 on MUCC/Conservation issues as well as popular culture.
  - 1950-1958 (Volume 1)
    (includes clippings photographs; the scrapbook was maintained by Harry R. Gaines)
  - 1958-1959 (Volume 2)
    (contains clippings, pamphlets, scattered correspondence, and miscellaneous administrative materials)
    (stored in box)